Eat Lumine is opening today at Shinjuku Station!
New gourmet spot in the station on the first basement floor of Shinjuku Station
EATRUMINE opens today!
The first financier to open in Tokyo
Butaman, the first Lumine store to open in Tokyo
and Japanese sweets only available at Eat Lumine.
There are 28 stores in the eTourmine!
Today, let's check out the delicious stores at eTourmine that opened today!
First of all
Wow, there are so many breads lined up!
Baker's Symphony is
A select store featuring breads from over 100 brands from 3 pits!
More than 1000 kinds of breads from Tokyo, Chiba and other cities are gathered.
It is one of the largest bread select stores in Japan!
We have croissants made with the best yeast and
Sponge cake bread made with wheat from Shonan
Olive pocaccia with a sticky texture.
Among them, we recommend
This pudding-inspired bread
It is very popular at the store with a long line in Saitama.
This fluffy bread is made in the image of pudding
White chocolate and other ingredients are added to the dough
and caramelized to give it a sweetness
to give it a pudding-like flavor.
When baked in the oven
the inside is sweet and fluffy like a pudding.
Mercer Bake Shop offers chiffon cakes by Mercer Service
into a gap cake that is easy to take home on the train.
Sweet and sour strawberry or crunchy oreo
We recommend the caramel flavor
The fluffy texture of the dough is topped with
When you try it, you will be surprised
The fluffy caramel is rich and bittersweet
It goes perfectly with the milky cream and chiffon cake
Yamamotoyama, famous for its nori seaweed, has opened its first restaurant specializing in rice balls and ochazuke
Using three kinds of nori seaweed
and chazuke with nori that can be tasted in a tea broth made by combining Daichi tea and dashi (Japanese soup stock)
You can enjoy onigiri made with Yamagata Prefecture's fly and ground laver! You can enjoy onigiri made with Yamagata fly and ground seaweed!
I recommend the plum onigiri.
Actually, inside is
Ariake nori with rich tsukudani and ume plum
Ariake nori tsukudani with crunchy ume plum
The seaweed wrapped around it is also from Ariake
Finally, topped with a crunchy plum chip, it's a plum rice ball like no other!
The nori is made with a sweet and elegant flavor!
You can also enjoy the crispy texture of the plums!